KINERET **ASIYAHAN**





PROFILE

Full stack developer JUNIOR

assertive, goal- oriented, excellent interpersonal & communication skills, solid work ethic, proven experience in professional positions requiring the ability to work independently, as part of a team in shift and team management. Experience as the director of a computer network in the IDF.



EDUCATION AND VOCATIONAL TRAINING

2021 | Tech Career - Technology Training Center

Web / win application programming and development course 800-hour course

Course contents:

Server Side: C #, Asp.Net MVC, Nodejs OOP, API Using Express Client-side: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Bootstrap, Nodejs Development environment: visual studio code, visual studio

Database: MONOGDB, MSSQL.

2018 | Double-entry Accounting. BDO-College Academic College of Finance 2011-2014 | Pelech High School Kiryat Ekron .

Graduate, Communication Program



EXPERIENCE

2019-2020 | Caspit Payment Technologies

Senior Position - responsible for providing technical support and customer service.

2015-2017 | "Tamnoon" Fashion Chain

Was in charge of employees, shift /sales & meeting network goals.



MILITARY SERVICE

2015-2017 | Director of the Computer Network Home Front Command

The position required technical skills, service delivery, self-discipline, meeting deadlines and dealing with stressful situations.

During my military service, I took a cyber security manager's course.



LANGUAGES

Mother tongues: Hebrew & Amharic. English: good level

References available on request